<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Stories</string>
    <string name="stella_young">Stella Young</string>
    <string name="stella_subtitle">I am not your inspiration, thank you very much</string>
    <string name="stella_description">Stella Young is a comedian and journalist who happens to go about her day in a wheelchair — a fact that doesn\'t, she\'d like to make clear, automatically turn her into a noble inspiration to all humanity. In this very funny talk, Young breaks down society\'s habit of turning disabled people into "inspiration porn."</string>
    <string name="stella_link">Tap here to listen.</string>
    <string name="stella_url">https://www.ted.com/talks/stella_young_i_m_not_your_inspiration_thank_you_very_much/transcript?language=en</string>
    <string name="julian">Julian\'s Story</string>
    <string name="julian_subtitle">Pride in sign language</string>
    <string name="julian_description">Julian, an African American Caucasian boy who is deaf describes his experiences at the Washington School for the Deaf, and explains why people should learn to sign.</string>
    <string name="julian_link">Tap here to watch.</string>
    <string name="julian_url"><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Iz3_n5g4LRs&ab_channel=OfficeoftheEducationOmbuds]]></string>
    <string name="warren">Warren\'s Story</string>
    <string name="warren_subtitle">Tools for school with ADHD</string>
    <string name="warren_description">Student with disability Warren Lybbert, a 9th grader at Quincy High School, describes in his own voice the challenges he faces and how assistive technology helps him.</string>
    <string name="warren_link">Tap here to watch.</string>
    <string name="warren_url"><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PJ7jK_IyOPs&ab_channel=OfficeoftheEducationOmbuds]]></string>
    <string name="kenassa">Kenassa\'s Story</string>
    <string name="kenassa_subtitle">Expression with Autism</string>
    <string name="kenassa_description">Kenassa, a Japanese, Chinese and Oromo (East African) student with disabilities talks about his experiences at school, and explains how Autism is a way of understanding from a different perspective.</string>
    <string name="kenassa_link">Tap here to view.</string>
    <string name="kenassa_url"><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZUzupiG1D3Y&ab_channel=OfficeoftheEducationOmbuds]]></string>
    <string name="AJ">AJ\'s Story</string>
    <string name="AJ_subtitle">Wheeling towards inclusion</string>
    <string name="AJ_description">Middle school student with disability Angelina (A.J.) Gammons-Reese, a 7th grade African American of Haitian decent at Meridian Parent Partnership Program,  describe in their own voice the challenges they face and their desire to be included.</string>
    <string name="AJ_link">Tap here to watch.</string>
    <string name="AJ_url"><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1XQyuMHUwrc&ab_channel=OfficeoftheEducationOmbuds]]></string>
    <string name="anna">Anna\'s Story</string>
    <string name="anna_subtitle">Blindness is more of a social disability than a physical disability</string>
    <string name="anna_description">Anna, a 12th grader at Issaquah High School shares her experiences as a student with disabilities and her hopes for the future.</string>
    <string name="anna_link">Tap here to watch</string>
    <string name="anna_url"><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8GrgEOsfl_M&ab_channel=OfficeoftheEducationOmbuds]]></string>
    <string name="DJ">DJ Savarese</string>
    <string name="DJ_subtitle">Text-to-voice independence</string>
    <string name="DJ_description">Abandoned by his birth parents and presumed incompetent, DJ Savarese (“Deej”) found not only a loving family but also a life in words, which he types on a text-to-voice synthesizer. As he makes his way through high school and dreams of college, he confronts the terrors of his past, society\'s obstacles to inclusion, and the sometimes paralyzing beauty of his own senses. In his advocacy on behalf of other nonspeaking autistics, he embraces filmmaking and poetry, and discovers what having a voice can truly mean.</string>
    <string name="DJ_link">Tap here to learn more.</string>
    <string name="DJ_url">https://www.deejmovie.com/</string>
    <string name="owen">Owen Suskind</string>
    <string name="owen_subtitle">Expression via Disney with Autism</string>
    <string name="owen_description">By evocatively interweaving classic Disney sequences with verité scenes from Owen’s life, the film explores how identification and empathy with characters like Simba, Jafar, and Ariel create a context for him to understand his feelings and interpret reality. Beautiful, original animations further give form to Owen’s rich dialogue with all the Disney classics as he imagines himself heroically facing adversity in a tribe of sidekicks.</string>
    <string name="owen_link">Tap to watch the documentary</string>
    <string name="owen_url"><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oVMcYkRHtcU&ab_channel=YouTubeMovies]]></string>
    <string name="background_description">Image of speaker</string>
</resources>